<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ViewModel3</string>
    <string name="devils_peek">Devil\'s Peek</string>
    <string name="mother_may_i">Mother May I?</string>
    <string name="scream6">Scream 6</string>
    <string name="paint">Paint</string>
    <string name="TheShawshankRedemption">The Shawshank Redemption</string>
    <string name="theGodfather">The Godfather</string>
    <string name="AngryMan">12 Angry Man</string>
    <string name="ninja">Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles:Mutant Madness</string>
    <string name="theFlash">The Flash</string>
    <string name="guardiansOfGalaxy">Guardions Of The Galaxy Vol:3</string>
    <string name="transformers">Transformers: Rise of The Beasts</string>
    <string name="fightClub">Fight Club</string>
    <string name="forestGump">Forest Gump</string>
    <string name="inception">Inception</string>
    <string name="interstellar">İnterstellar</string>
    <string name="starWars">Star Wars: Rise of The Emperor</string>
    <string name="theMatrix">The Matrix</string>
    <string name="sevenSamurai">Seven Samurai</string>
    <string name="hannibal">Hannibal : Silence of the Lambs</string>
    <string name="greenMile">Green Mile</string>
    <string name="action">Action</string>
    <string name="adventure">Adventure</string>
    <string name="animation">Animation</string>
    <string name="crime">Crime</string>
    <string name="scifi">Sci_Fi</string>
    <string name="horror">Horror</string>
    <string name="drama">Drama</string>
    <string name="fantasy">Fantastik</string>
    <string name="NULL">NULL</string>
    <string name="biog">Biyography</string>
    <string name="pisi">Psychologic</string>
    <string name="green_mile_detail">Miracles can happen in the most unexpected places, even in a solitary cell of Cold Mountain Penitentiary... John Coffey is a convict with supernatural powers, and Tom Hanks is an officer at this prison.</string>
    <string name="hannibal_detail">" Adapted from the novel of the same name by Thomas Harris and brought to the silver screen, this 1991 psychological thriller is directed by Jonathan Demme. In this gripping adaptation of Thomas J. Harris's novel, Clarice Starling (Jodie Foster), an FBI trainee, delves into the depths of the twisted mind of Hannibal Lecter (Anthony Hopkins), a psychiatrist turned cannibalistic serial killer, by entering a high-security asylum. Starling needs clues to catch a serial killer, but unfortunately, her Faustian relationship with Lecter leads to his escape, allowing two separate serial killers to roam freely in the darkness. Nominated for seven Academy Awards in 1992, the film secured golden statuettes for its director and lead actors, as well as winning Best Film and Best Adapted Screenplay. Jodie Foster, who played the lead role, joined the ranks of actors who won two Oscars before turning 30. Anthony Hopkins won the Best Actor Oscar for his 16-minute performance in this film, marking the shortest screen time for an actor in a film. It is the only horror film to win the Best Film Oscar. A sequel titled \"Hannibal,\" directed by Ridley Scott, was released in 2001."</string>
    <string name="seven_detail">"A group of villagers, who witness the courage and selflessness of the master samurai Kambei, implore him to protect their villages that are constantly raided by bandits. Despite having no personal gain in mind, Kambei agrees and first takes on Katsushiro, a young samurai who becomes his disciple, and later Kikuchiyo, who initially appears to be a warrior but is revealed to be a farmer's son with a passion for combat. As Kambei adds four more samurai to his team and embarks on defending the village, he is warmly welcomed by the villagers and gains their affection. He begins to teach them how to defend themselves. Meanwhile, the bandits lurk at the village's borders, waiting for the right moment to launch new attacks.  Considered the pinnacle of Akira Kurosawa's career, Seven Samurai, despite its three-hour-plus duration, contains numerous details in its war and \"action\" scenes that would engage even the least attentive viewer, especially given the scarcity of quality examples from that era. It is a masterpiece that maintains the integrity of its storytelling and cinematic quality, never compromising on either aspect.     "</string>
    <string name="matrix_detail">" When a captivating stranger leads the computer hacker Neo into a challenging underworld, they discover a startling truth - the life Neo knows is an intricate deception orchestrated by a malevolent cyber intelligence."</string>
    <string name="starwars_detail">" With the assistance of Darth Vader, the Emperor strives to gain control of the universe by crushing the rebels. Through their deployed spy droids, they discover that the rebels' base is on the planet Hoth, leading them to dispatch their forces there. Luke Skywalker, Han Solo, and Princess Leia narrowly escape to Cloud City. Meanwhile, Luke sets out on a journey to find Yoda and complete his Jedi training. Will our heroes come together to defeat the Emperor?"</string>
    <string name="interstellar_detail">As life on Earth comes to an end, a group of researchers takes on the most crucial mission in human history: embarking on a journey beyond our galaxy to explore whether humanity can continue its existence beyond the stars. Cooper, a technically skilled and resourceful individual, struggles to make a living as a farmer in cornfields. His sole purpose in life is to provide a secure future for his two children. Living with them, his father-in-law Donald watches over the children, while his 10-year-old daughter Murph possesses an astonishing intellect. Missing his former career as a scientist, Cooper unexpectedly receives an offer one day, leading his family, and more importantly, all of humanity, to face a challenging decision. The film is inspired by Kip S. Thorne\'s theory that \"wormholes\" could truly exist in the universe, potentially enabling time travel.</string>
    <string name="inception_detail">Dom Cobb (Leonardo DiCaprio) is an exceptionally skilled thief. His expertise lies in the vulnerable moment of dream perception, where he extracts and steals valuable secrets from the depths of the subconscious... Cobb\'s rare ability has turned him into a sought-after player in the dangerous new world of corporate espionage. However, this situation has also made him an international fugitive and cost him everything he loves... Cobb is presented with an opportunity that could free him from his predicament. He\'s offered one last job that could give him his life back, assuming he can complete the impossible \"inception\"...  Instead of the perfect heist, Cobb and his team of professionals must do the exact opposite this time; their task is not to steal an idea but to plant it. If they succeed, this will be the perfect crime. However, no amount of meticulous planning or expertise can prepare them against their dangerous adversaries who seem to predict their every move. Their enemy is someone whose arrival only Cobb can foresee...</string>
    <string name="forest_detail">Forrest is a disabled child. However, this disability doesn\'t dull his desire to become a regular person. Over a span of thirty years, Forrest faces incredible challenges, eventually becoming one of his country\'s most beloved football stars. His efforts don\'t stop there; he becomes a hero returning from the Vietnam War and receives a Medal of Honor at the White House. But most importantly, he manages to win the heart of the person he loves most in the world and marries her. Despite not being very smart, Forrest knows exactly what his heart wants. With extraordinary effort, he becomes an example to everyone that they can achieve what they desire.</string>
    <string name="fight_detail">The unnamed narrator (Norton) is an insomniac employee at a car company who is suffering from sleep deprivation. His doctor refuses to give him more medication and suggests he attend a support group for assistance. The narrator joins a support group for testicular cancer victims, where he meets Marla; she also attends the group even though, like the narrator, she is not actually ill. After returning from a business trip, he finds his apartment destroyed due to an explosion. He calls Tyler Durden (Brad Pitt), a soap salesman he met during his travels, and they meet at a bar. After a few drinks, they go outside, where Tyler provokes the narrator to hit him. This fight will completely change the narrator\'s life.</string>
    <string name="transformers_detail">Transformers: Rise of the Beasts,\" Predacons, Maximals, and Terrorcons will be introduced into the Transformers universe. The film will be set with a retro vibe reminiscent of the 90s. The other Transformers, Autobots, and Decepticons will emerge in the midst of the ongoing conflict.</string>
    <string name="guardian_detail">Guardians of the Galaxy 3,\" directed by James Gunn, marks the conclusion of the Guardians universe with its latest installment. In the sequel to the Guardians of the Galaxy series, the origins of Rocket Raccoon and the journey of Gamora\'s return will be explored.</string>
    <string name="flash_detail">Flash, to prevent his mother\'s murder, goes back in time and significantly disrupts the timeline.</string>
    <string name="ninja_detail">Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem,\" begins as the turtle brothers, who have been hidden from the human world for years, take action to win the hearts of the New York public through their heroic deeds and desire to live among them as normal teenagers. As they strive for this goal, their journalist friend April O\'Neil, who takes on the task of introducing them to the public, helps them battle a mysterious criminal organization. However, before long, they realize they\'ve bitten off more than they can chew when a formidable mutant army is unleashed against them.</string>
    <string name="angry_detail">A jury attempts to prevent the miscarriage of justice by compelling their peers to reexamine the evidence.</string>
    <string name="father_detail">The Corleone family, who emigrated from Sicily, continues their efforts to settle in America. However, as they face attempts of brute force from certain unidentified individuals who demand extortion from every venture they undertake, the Corleones also start using force to counter them, succeeding and finding themselves immersed in a lifestyle they could never have imagined. Balancing their rigid traditions and family life with ruthlessly eliminating those who cross their path, the Corleone family eventually becomes the most feared mafia organization in America. Despite claiming they are not a mafia but a family, their actions speak otherwise.</string>
    <string name="esaret_detail">Andy Dufresne, a young and successful banker, is sentenced to life in Shawshank prison for the murder of his wife and her lover.</string>
    <string name="paint_detail">Vermont\'s number 1 public television painter, Carl Nargle, believes he has everything: a signature palette, a custom-made minivan, and devoted fans hanging on his every stroke... until a younger, better artist steals everything (and everyone) Carl holds dear.</string>
    <string name="scream_detail">In this installment of the series, four survivors who escaped the Ghostface murders leave Woodsboro behind and attempt to start a new chapter in New York City.</string>
    <string name="mother_detail">Emmett enters a nightmarish therapy game with his estranged wife, Anya, who has mysteriously taken on the personality of his recently deceased mother.</string>
    <string name="devil_detail">In the Appalachian Mountains of North Carolina, Jacob McNeely is torn between working for his meth-dealing mob boss father or leaving the mountains forever with the girl he loves.</string>
</resources>